(Howard:)Can we just all agree
we're worried about Affleck?
(Stuart:)Sure.
Yeah, of course.
(Adam:)What's an Affleck?
(Sheldon:)Is there a reason I had
to leave my own apartment?
(Amy:)Well, I think
they just want you to see it
(Amy:)for the first time
all decorated.
(Sheldon:)But who's gonna tell them
they're doing it wrong?
(Amy:)Well, I'm... I'm sure they'll
ask you to give a speech,
(Amy:)and that's when
you just tear 'em a new one.
(Amy:)Have to say, you...
(Amy:)you do look good in that suit.
(Sheldon:)Oh. Thank you.
(Amy:)Maybe later I'll, uh...
(Amy:)get to see you
in your birthday suit.
But this is my
birthday suit.
(Sheldon:)Are you having a stroke?
(Sheldon:)Because that's the kind of thing
(Sheldon:)that just ruins
a birthday party.
(Leonard:)So, Mother, I'm surprised
you came all this way
(Leonard:)for Sheldon's birthday.
(Beverley:)Oh, I was happy to.
(Beverley:)He did come to my 60th.